

FAITH SCHUBERT

ABOUT ME

I am an experienced teacher aspiring to use all of my transferable skills from the classroom to build a new career in customer experience. After 5 years working as an educator and another 5 years in client-facing environments, I've learned that in my natural state I'm a product evangelist who loves to help people solve problems.

CONTACT

faithelizabeth26@gmail.com



+52 322 319 8206

EDUCATION

B.A. Applied Linguistics Trinity Western University

State of Washington Education Certificate Endorsement in Elementary Education

INTERESTS

Linguistics

UX Design

Travel

Health & Wellness

SKILLS

- Working in a fast paced, dead-line driven environment
- Managing multiple projects simultaneously
- Using interpersonal skills to collaborate in a diplomatic and patient manner with teammates and administrators
- Conducting interviews and facilitating complaint resolution with clients
- Independently researching solutions to complex problems
- Collecting and analyzing data to evaluate the effectiveness of those solutions
- Developing and documenting classroom and school-wide procedures
- Training new teachers to implement school-wide procedures

TEACHING EXPERIENCE

Teacher, Grades 2 & 5

British American School Puerto Vallarta, Jalisco, Mexico August 2017 - June 2019

Certified Teacher, Grade 3

Martin Luther King, Jr. Elementary School Yakima, Washington, USA August 2016 - 2017

Teacher, Preschool

Migrant Education Even Start Yakima, Washington, USA March 2011 - January 2013

ODD JOBS











Ice Cream Shop 2005

Medical Records 2008

Consignment Store 2010

Public Library 2011

Homeless Shelter 2013